advertlets.com 2014-06-29

# Advertlets.com » Putting the ‘bling’ in ‘blogging’ » Privacy Policy and Terms

## User Information

All users who receive an ad served by Advertlets retain complete anonymity where Advertlets is concerned. As ads are delivered, Advertlets does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private property. Advertlets does, however, collect information that is specific to how you use the Internet. Advertlets servers note non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring a given ad’s effectiveness on behalf of Advertlets clients and customers.

There are instances where a user may provide specific personal information in response to an ad containing a poll, purchase agreement, or registration questionnaire. For such programs, Advertlets (or a third party working in conjunction with Advertlets and the advertiser) acquires this information on behalf of the advertiser client. The client uses this information to deliver the goods or services requested by the user. When requested, Advertlets may employ this information in a compiled format without identifying users specifically to provide to the advertiser client precise profiles of the types of individuals responding to the ads.

## The Cookie Principle

### Advertlets Network Publishers:

Advertlets may use cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. When you are first served an Advertlets ad, Advertlets may assign a unique random number to your computer browser – commonly known as a "cookie." We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this number lets us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over – thus enhancing your online Web viewing experience. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire.

## Third-Party Measurement Services

Often, advertisers will employ a third-party service provider other than Advertlets for serving the advertisements and for tracking the performance of an ad program. These companies may employ cookie and 1×1 pixel technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their client. These companies may collect and use anonymous information about your visits to our member Websites and other Websites. The information collected can include:

  1. Date/time of your visit
  2. The banner ad that was shown
  3. Their cookie
  4. Your IP address

This information can also be used for online preference marketing (â€œprofilingâ€) purposes.

In these instances, Advertlets has no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned.

If you are a Advertlets Network Publisher and have questions regarding different third-party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please contact us via our contact form or at info@advertlets.com.

## Personal Information

### Advertlets Network Publishers:

Advertlets regards all personal information collected from its Web publisher members as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during registration processes and financial account information. Advertlets does offer to advertisers any data which may facilitate the sale of advertising for a member site. This includes traffic data, click-thru rates, unique visitor information, Web site geographic location, content information, and any demographic & profiling information offered by the Web site member for the purpose of facilitating an advertising sale.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this [link ](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/S/SSL.html).  

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [info@advertlets.com](mailto:info@advertlets.com)

## Disclosure

Advertlets openly volunteers its practices of collecting information, its targeting capabilities, and its use of cookies. If you are an Advertlets network publisher and have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to info@advertlets.com

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can be done by logging into your user account and updating your personal information or discontinuing service at anytime. Please note that we require your personal details to verify identity and for you to receive payment.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.

## Advertlets.com

E-mail at: [info@advertlets.com](mailto:info@advertlets.com),

or by phone at +603-78049282.

or use our contact form here.

`
